<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Teleprompter‏</string>
    <string name="demo_title">Demo Show</string>

    <string name="demo_text">Real sold my in call. Invitation on an advantages collecting. But event old above shy bed noisy. Had sister see wooded favour income has. Stuff rapid since do as hence. Too insisted ignorant procured remember are believed yet say finished.

Dissuade ecstatic and properly saw entirely sir why laughter endeavor. In on my jointure horrible margaret suitable he followed speedily. Indeed vanity excuse or mr lovers of on. By offer scale an stuff. Blush be sorry no sight. Sang lose of hour then he left find.

Seen you eyes son show. Far two unaffected one alteration apartments celebrated but middletons interested. Described deficient applauded consisted my me do. Passed edward two talent effect seemed engage six. On ye great do child sorry lived. Proceed cottage far letters ashamed get clothes day. Stairs regret at if matter to. On as needed almost at basket remain. By improved sensible servants children striking in surprise.

He share of first to worse. Weddings and any opinions suitable smallest nay. My he houses or months settle remove ladies appear. Engrossed suffering supposing he recommend do eagerness. Commanded no of depending extremity recommend attention tolerably. Bringing him smallest met few now returned surprise learning jennings. Objection delivered eagerness he exquisite at do in. Warmly up he nearer mr merely me.

Old unsatiable our now but considered travelling impression. In excuse hardly summer in basket misery. By rent an part need. At wrong  of water those linen. Needed oppose seemed how all. Very mrs shed shew gave you. Oh shutters do removing reserved wandered an. But described questions for recommend advantage belonging estimable had. Pianoforte reasonable as so am inhabiting. Chatty design remark and his abroad figure but its.

She literature discovered increasing how diminution understood. Though and highly the enough county for man. Of it up he still court alone widow seems. Suspected he remainder rapturous my sweetness. All vanity regard sudden nor simple can. World mrs and vexed china since after often.

Promotion an ourselves up otherwise my. High what each snug rich far yet easy. In companions inhabiting mr principles at insensible do. Heard their sex hoped enjoy vexed child for. Prosperous so occasional assistance it discovered especially no. Provision of he residence consisted up in remainder arranging described. Conveying has concealed necessary furnished bed zealously immediate get but. Terminated as middletons or by instrument. Bred do four so your felt with. No shameless principle dependent household do.

If wandered relation no surprise of screened doubtful. Overcame no insisted ye of trifling husbands. Might am order hours on found. Or dissimilar companions friendship impossible at diminution. Did yourself carriage learning she man its replying. Sister piqued living her you enable mrs off spirit really. Parish oppose repair is me misery. Quick may saw style after money mrs.

Sportsman do offending supported extremity breakfast by listening. Decisively advantages nor expression unpleasing she led met. Estate was tended ten boy nearer seemed. As so seeing latter he should thirty whence. Steepest speaking up attended it as. Made neat an on be gave show snug tore.

Do am he horrible distance marriage so although. Afraid assure square so happen mr an before. His many same been well can high that. Forfeited did law eagerness allowance improving assurance bed. Had saw put seven joy short first. Pronounce so enjoyment my resembled in forfeited sportsman. Which vexed did began son abode short may. Interested astonished he at cultivated or me. Nor brought one invited she produce her.

</string>
    <string name="enter_title">enter title</string>
    <string name="add_your_text">add your text</string>
    <string name="add_dialog">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel_dialog">@android:string/cancel</string>


    <!-- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
         - Used by Preferences  -
         - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -->
    <string name="pref_horizontal_mode_label">Horizontal Mode</string>
    <string name="pref_horizontal_mode_key" translatable="false">horizontal_mode</string>
    <string name="pref_true">on</string>
    <string name="pref_false">of</string>

    <!-- Label for the show mid range checkbox preference -->
    <string name="pref_timer_key_label">Show Timer</string>
    <string name="pref_timer_key" translatable="false">show_mid_range</string>

    <!-- Label for the show treble checkbox preference -->
    <string name="pref_show_treble_label">Show Treble</string>
    <!-- Key name for storing treble in SharedPreferences -->
    <string name="pref_show_treble_key" translatable="false">show_treble</string>

    <!-- Summary for Checkboxes -->


    <!-- Label for the size preference -->
    <string name="pref_size_label">Size Multiplier</string>

    <!-- Key name for storing size in SharedPreferences -->
    <string name="pref_size_key" translatable="false">size</string>

    <!-- Default for size preference -->
    <string name="pref_size_default" translatable="false">1</string>


    <!-- Label for the color preference -->
    <string name="pref_color_label">Shape Color</string>

    <!-- Label for red color preference -->
    <string name="pref_color_label_red">Red</string>
    <!-- Label for blue color preference -->
    <string name="pref_color_label_blue">Blue</string>
    <!-- Label for green color preference -->
    <string name="pref_color_label_green">Green</string>

    <!-- Key name for color preference in SharedPreferences -->
    <string name="pref_color_key" translatable="false">color</string>

    <!-- Value in SharedPreferences for red color option -->
    <string name="pref_color_red_value" translatable="false">red</string>

    <!-- Value in SharedPreferences for blue color option -->
    <string name="pref_color_blue_value" translatable="false">blue</string>

    <!-- Value in SharedPreferences for green color option -->
    <string name="pref_color_green_value" translatable="false">green</string>
    <string name="search">search</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="edit">edit</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="select">select</string>
    <string name="delete_all">Delete All</string>
    <string name="slow">slow</string>
    <string name="fast">fast</string>
    <string name="set_colors">set colors</string>
    <string name="toggle_marker">Toggle marker</string>
    <string name="defaults">default</string>
    <string name="undo">undo</string>
    <string name="empty_text">Please click on one of the items to start viewing</string>
    <string name="etc">etc ...............................................................................................................</string>

</resources>
